我是哪里不对？ 我看起来不够有趣吗？
What is it about me? Do I not look fun enough?
我是有哪里讨人厌吗？
Is there something repellent about me?
派对好玩吗？
How was the party?
太糟糕了 有个女人简直无视我
It couldn't have been worse. A woman literally passed through me.
我有那么不讨人喜欢吗？
What is it? Am I hideously unattractive?
不，你非常讨人喜欢
No,you are not. You are very attractive.
我也是一样
I go through the same thing.
每当我增加了一点点重量 我就开始质疑一切了
When I put on a little weight,I question everything.
你说我变胖了？
I've put on weight?
你要…？
Did you want to...?
不是，不是重量 说绝缘体比较恰当
No,not weight. More like insulation.
钱德，我正在失业 迫切需要做点事情
I'm unemployed,in dire need of a project.
你要不要运动？我可以重塑你
Wanna work out? I can remake you.
我很想，但那或许会妨碍 我那些无所事事的时间
I would,but that might get in the way of my lying-around time.
拜托啦
Please?
对啦，让她做一下嘛
Come on,let her do it!
好吧…
All right.
但我穿上紧身衣后 胸部比你大的话，我就不来了
If we put on spandex and my boobs are bigger than yours,I'm going home.
你的胸部很好呀
Your boobs are fine.
听着，我刚才不该乱说话的
I shouldn't have said anything.
过来…
Come here. Come here!
双手都合不起来了
Can't make hands meet!
The One Where Ross Finds Out
六人行 第2季 第07集 罗斯发现了
好，开始吧
Let's do it!
怎么了？
What?
没什么 只是没看过你穿紧身裤而已呀
Nothing. Just never seen your little stretchy pants before.
很可爱
It's cute.
我去换衣服
And we're changing.
加油，再做五个
Come on,give me five more!
再五个
Five more!
再做五个就给你看胸部
Five more and I'll flash you.
一…
One...
…二…
...two...
…二点五
...two and a half.
好了，给我看一边吧
Just show me one of them.
中央公园
她疯了
She's insane!
那个女人疯了
The woman is insane.
上班前，上班后，上班中
It's before work,after work,and during work.
她叫我在公司做收臀运动
She's got me doing butt-clenches at my desk.
现在，他们不再送邮件给我了
And now they won't bring me my mail anymore.
告诉她停止不就行了
Tell her to stop.
不，她被解雇了我现在是她的全部
No, while she's unemployed I'm all she's got.
我们为什么不凑钱给她买个饭店？
Why don't we all pitch in and buy her a restaurant?
菲比，你昨晚跟史考怎么样？
Hey,Pheebs. How'd it go with Scott?
不错呀 带他去了一家浪漫的餐厅…
It was nice. Took him to a romantic restaurant...
…点了香槟，很好
...ordered champagne. Nice.
那个家伙还是不行动啊？
He still won't put out?
不，零蛋，没有
Nope. Zilch. Nothing.
真遗憾，菲比
Sorry,Pheebs.
我不在乎慢慢的来
Look,I don't mind taking it slow.
我很喜欢他
I like him a lot.
他这个人很有趣，人也很甜
He's really interesting,and he's really sweet.
他干嘛那么矜持呢？
Why won't he give it up?
或许他跟我们开车的方向相反
Maybe he drives his car on the other side of the road.
你懂我的意思吧？
If you know what I mean.
不懂，他又不是英国人
No. What do you mean? He's not British.
他或许是同性恋
Maybe he's gay.
不，我觉得问题不在那儿
I don't think that's the problem.
因为我们前几天去跳舞…
We went dancing the other night...
…他紧紧抱住我的那个样子 还有他凝视我眼睛的样子…
...and just the way he held me so close and looked into my eyes....
我觉得他对我绝对有意思
I just definitely felt something.
是啊，从眼神能看出多少呢？
But how much can you tell from a look?
不，我是从屁股感觉到的
I felt it on my hip. I could tell.
唷，宾，二十分钟后打壁球
Yo,Bing! Racquetball in 20 minutes.
乔伊，好兄弟 举起我的手赏她一巴掌
Joey,be a pal. Lift up my hand and smack her with it.
瑞秋，你别看
Oh,Rachel! Don't look.
什么？
What?
我才不在乎 我今晚有约会
I don't care. I have a date tonight.
你有约会？
You have a date?
对呀，莫妮卡为我安排的
Monica's setting me up.
那罗斯跟…
What about Ross and....
我嫉妒的那件事吗？
What? My whole insane jealousy thing?
虽然那还挺有趣的…
Well,you know,as much fun as that was...
…我决定不再疯下去了
... I've decided to opt for sanity.
你真的不介意那些了？
You're okay about all this?
是的，我还要过我的日子呢
Oh,yeah,come on! I'm moving on.
他爱怎么把她压在那扇窗子上 就怎么压吧
He can press her up against that window as much as he wants.
干脆把她摔过窗子算了
For all I care,he can throw her through the damn thing.
各位
Hi,guys.
莫妮卡，我想明天早上过来拿以前的猫玩具
Monica,I'll come by tomorrow and pick up Fluffy's old cat toys,okay?
不讲全名就不给喔
If you say his full name.
好吧，那我明天可不可以过来拿多毛姆维顿猫的玩具？
Can I come over tomorrow and pick up Fluffy Meowington's cat toys?
没问题
All right.
你要养猫啊？ 事实上，是我们要养猫
-You're getting a cat? -Actually,we're getting a cat.
一起养？
Together?
你们两个？一起？
Both of you? Together?
我们想它会一半时间跟罗斯住 一半跟我住
It'll live with Ross half the time and with me half the time.
那是不是很棒呢
Well,isn't that just lovely?
那是一件你们两个…
That's something you'll enjoy...
…可以疼爱非常非常久的东西
...for a really,really,really long time.
希望如此
Hopefully.
我得走了 我有约会
Look at that. I gotta go! I got a date!
跟个男人喔
With a man.
祝各位今晚顺利…
You guys have a really good night...
…而你们两个得到一只好猫
...and you two have a really good cat.
我们是不允许拿走这些的
We're not supposed to take these when we leave.
我不晓得莫妮卡有没有告诉你 这是我离婚之后的第一次约会
I don't know if Monica told you,but this my first date since my divorce.
我显得有一点紧张…
If I seem a little nervous...
…那是真的
... I am.
猫能活多久啊？
How long do cats live?
你说什么？
I'm sorry?
猫，猫能活多久？
Cats. How long do they live?
如果不把它们丢到 巴士下面去送死的话
Figuring you don't throw them under a bus or something?
大概是十五，六年吧
Maybe 1 5,1 6 years.
那真是太棒了
Well,that's just great.
干杯
Cheers!
好，干杯
Right. Clink.
莫妮卡把我说得比本人可爱 对不对？
Monica told you I was cuter than this,didn't she?
不，麦克 不是因为你…
No,Michael,it's not you. Sorry. It's just....
我是…我另外有心事
It's this thing.
事情很糟…因为
It's not as bad as it sounds...
…我有一个朋友 他跟他的女朋友要养猫
... but this friend of mine is getting a cat with his girlfriend.
听起来的确是…
Oh,that does sound....
他们两个才刚刚开始交往不久
He just started going out with her.
他是你以前的男朋友吗？
Is this guy an old boyfriend?
他想得美喔
Yeah,he wishes.
对不起，你瞧瞧我
I'm sorry. Look at me.
好了，麦克，谈谈你吧
Michael,let's talk about you.
那么…
So....
以前你跟女朋友 一起养过宠物吗？
Did you ever get a pet with a girlfriend?
我知道为什么了 什么？
-So I figured it out. -What?
史考为什么不想跟我上床
Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me.
因为我不够性感
I'm not sexy enough.
菲比，别傻了
Phoebe,that's crazy.
第一次看到你之后 你知道我对钱德说什么吗？
When I first met you,you know what I said?
我说“完美的屁股，好身材”
I said,"Excellent butt,great rack."
真的？嘴好甜
Really? That's so sweet.
说实在的，我被冒犯了 可是感觉真好
I mean,I'm officially offended. But that's so sweet.
菲比，你想知道为什么的话 你必须开口去问他
If you wanna know what the deal is,you're gonna have to ask him.
你说得对…
You're right. You're right.
你真“可口”啊
You are so "yum"!
那是只猫 你知道的，猫
I mean,it's a cat,you know? It's a cat.
他们干嘛不养只昆虫 养只果蝇就好了
Why can't they get a bug? One of those fruit flies.
那种只活一，两天的东西
Those things that live for a day.
它们叫什么？
What are they called?
果蝇？
Fruit flies?
谢谢
Thank you.
要不要点甜点啊？
Would you like dessert?
不，不要了
No dessert.
我想结账，求你了
Just the check. Please.
你玩得不开心？
Oh,no. You're not having fun,are you?
不…我很开心
No,no,I am.
不过刚才那一个半小时 我都在回忆电影《餐馆》的情节
But only because I've been playing the movie Diner in my head.
你看我
Oh,look at me.
Look at me.
我在跟一个很棒的男人约会
I'm on a date with a really great guy.
却满脑子是罗斯…
All I can think about is Ross...
…跟他的猫…
...and his cat...
…还有他的茱莉
...and his Julie.
你想吃点派吗
Look, do you want a piece of pie?
不！太晚了，我已经把事情搞砸了
No！Too late for that, man.I've screwed this all up
我只是想忘了他 天啊，为什么我不能呢？
I just want to get over him. Why can't I do that?
听我说，我经历过离婚 相信我，不会有事的
Look,I've been through a divorce. Trust me,you're gonna be fine.
你还看不出来 因为你跟他还没有了结嘛…
You can't see it because you haven't had closure
了结！
Closure!
就是那个，我就需要那个
That's what it is! That's what I need!
天啊，你太棒了
God,you're brilliant!
我为什么没有想到？ 我要怎么了结？
Why didn't I think of that? How do I get that?
这没有一定的方法，这只是…
Well,there's no one way really,it's just....
你要用任何的方法 只要能让你对他说：
Whatever it takes so that you can finally say to him:
“我不在乎你了”就行了
"I'm over you."
不在乎你
Over you.
就是这个
That's what it is.
了结
Closure.
抱歉
Hello? Excuse me?
抱歉…
Excuse me. Hel
请稍等 对不起啊
-Hang on. -Excuse me?
什么？ 对不起
-What? -Hi. I'm sorry.
我需要跟你借一下电话
I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.
我正在讲耶 我看得出来
-I'm talking. -I see that.
我打一个电话就可以了 很快的，我甚至会付钱给你
One phone call,I'll be very quick. I'll even pay for it myself.
你对你的电话有点诡异耶
You're being a little weird about your phone.
我待会儿再打给你
I'll call you back.
谢了
Thank you.
我的人缘真好
I'm so good with people.
答录机
Machine.
我在等哔哔 太好了
-Just waiting for the beep. -Good.
罗斯，我是瑞秋
Ross! Hi,it's Rachel.
我只是打来说…
I'm just calling to say that...
…一切都很好
...everything's fine.
我为你…
And I'm really happy for you...
…还有你的猫感到高兴
...and your cat.
对了，我认为你应该给它起个名字叫麦克
Who,by the way,I think you should name Michael.
知道吗？你瞧 我在想名字…
You see there,I'm thinking of names...
…所以显然我不在乎你了
...so obviously I am over you.
我不在乎你了
I am over you.
这就是我那位朋友 所谓的“了结”
And that,my friend,is what they call "closure."
不
No, no, no...
莫妮卡，今天是星期天早上 星期天我绝不跑步
It's Sunday morning. I'm not running on a Sunday.
为什么？ 因为是星期天
-Why not? -Because it's Sunday!
是神的日子
It's God's day.
你说停我们就停
If you say stop,then we stop.
停
Stop.
不，别这样啦，我们不能停
No,come on! We can't stop!
还有三磅要减
We got three more pounds to go!
我是精力火车而你在车上
I am the energy train and you are on board!
你的约会怎么样啊？
And how was the date?
我记得有家餐厅
I think there was a restaurant.
我还记得有酒
I know there was wine.
事实上，茱莉在楼下叫计程车
Actually,Julie's getting a cab.
我想要拿猫玩具 莫妮卡有没有说…
I just need the cat toys. Did Monica say....
你为什么那样看我？
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
对不起，我不知道…
I'm sorry. I don't know,l....
我觉得我昨晚好像梦到你…
I feel like I dreamed about you last night...
…但我不记得了
... but I don't remember.
在这儿
There they are.
我们昨晚有通电话吗？ 你有没有打给我？
Did we speak on the phone? Did you call me?
没有，我昨晚住在茱莉那里
No. I stayed at Julie's last night.
事实上，我根本还没回家呢 你介意我听一下留言吗？
I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?
请便啊
Oh,yeah,go ahead.
瑞秋，我有你的留言
Rach,I got a message from you!
麦克是谁啊？
Who's Michael?
天啊
Oh,my God!
天啊，罗斯，把电话挂掉
Ross,no! Hang up the phone. Give me the phone!
电话给我…
Give me the
你不在乎我了
You're over me?
天啊
Oh,God!
你… 我的天啊…
-You're -Oh,God.
你不在乎我了？
You're over me?
你是什么时候…
When were you...
…在乎我的？
... under me?
瑞秋，你…？
Rachel,do you...?
我是说，你…你…？
I mean,were you?
什么？
What?
基本上…
Basically...
…最近我…
...Iately,I've....
我对你有一些感觉
I've sort of had feelings for you.
你对我有感觉？
You've had feelings for me?
那又怎样？你先对我有感觉的
So? You had feelings for me first!
你知道我…
You know about my You know I had
我是说，你知道我有…
You know?
钱德告诉我的
Chandler told me.
钱德，他什么时候，什么时候，什么时候…
When did he? When did he? When did he?
你在中国的时候
When you were in China.
认识茱莉时
Meeting Julie.
茱莉？茱莉？那… 天啊
Julie. That's Oh,God!
我需要躺下来
I need to lie down.
不，你知道，我要站着
No,I'm gonna stand.
我要站着…
I'm gonna stand...
…我要踱步 我踱步，而且我站着
...and I'm gonna walk. I'm walking and I am standing.
现在你不在乎我了？
Now you're over me?
你还在乎我吗？
Are you over me?
那…那是茱莉
That's Julie.
茱莉 甜心，计程车在等喔
-Hi,Julie. -I've got a cab waiting.
我马上下来
I'll be right down!
等等，你要走了？
Wait,so you're going?
对，我得走 我现在没有办法谈这个
Well,okay,I have to. I can't deal with this right now.
计程车在等着
I mean,I've You know,I've got a cab.
我有女朋友 我要去领养一只猫
I've got a girlfriend. I'm gonna go get a cat.
猫
Cat!
乔伊 菲比
-Hey,Joey. -Hey,Pheebs.
你为什么在看 犹太牧师弹电吉他？
How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?
我找不到遥控器
I can't find the remote.
谢谢
Thank you.
对了，史考约我去他家午餐 我去了
Scott asked me to come over for lunch and I did.
然后… 我们做了
-And? -And we did.
正点，菲比好耶
All right! Way to go!
对呀
Yea,me!
怎么发生的？
So how did it happen?
我听了你的建议 问他到底怎么回事啊？
I took your advice and asked him what was going on.
那他说什么？
What did he say?
他了解性对女人而言呢 可以说是一件非常情绪化的事
He understands how sex can be a very emotional thing for a woman.
他只是怕我会变得像…
And he was just afraid that I was going to get all:
“第二天是否会打电话给我” “我们会有结局吗”之类的
"ls he gonna call me the next day?" and "Where is this going?"
所以他说他想等到 他准备开始认真了以后再说
So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be serious.
所以我说“放轻松好吗？”
So I said,"Okay. Relax,please."
我是说，性可以只是 两个人一时的感觉
Sex can be just about two people right there in the moment.
若他想再见我可以打电话给我 如果不想的话也没关系
If he wants to see me again,he can call. If not,that's fine too.
所以在长谈之后…
So after a lot of talking...
…我说服他了
... I convinced him.
让我先搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
他让你求他跟你上床
He got you to beg to sleep with him.
他让你说 他永远不用再打电话给你
He got you to say he never has to call you again.
而且还让你觉得 这是一个好主意？
And he got you thinking this is a great idea?
我简直崇拜他
This man is my god!
哦，这只太可爱了，你觉得呢
Oh, this one's cute.Don't you think？
是的，这只也是，那只也是
Yeah, and this one, and that one.
它们都太可爱了，它们这些小猫咪，选一只就好了
They're all cute. They're kittens.Just wrap one up.
-你同意吗？-我吗？
-You okay?.-Yeah, me?.
是的，是的，是吗？
Yeah, yeah. Yeah?.
罗斯，亲爱的
Ross, honey. Hey.
我知道这是一大步，但是我想我们会很好的
I know this is a big step,but I think we'll be okay.
是的，我知道，我知道
Yeah, I know. I know.
你们有没有特别老或者得了不知名疾病的猫
So do you have any cats that are really old or incredibly sick?.
我不想要那种马上就要死的
I don't want one that's about to die.
我们应该来这里之前就商量好的
We should've worked that out before we came down here.
好吧，亲爱的
Okay, sweetie.
我把范围缩小一下，这只
I'll narrow it down to this one here...
和这只带斑纹的
...and this one with the stripes.
你挑一只
You pick.
喔，嘿，我挑？
Whoa, hey, I have to pick?.
是的，挑一只你想要的
Yeah, whichever one you want.
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
这个可不容易
It's not that easy to choose.
所有的猫都很漂亮
Both cats are beautiful...
并且可爱
...and funny.
我确定我对每只猫都很满意
I' m sure I'd be happy with either cat.
-那么，你想两个都要？-两个？两个？
-Well, do you want to take both?.-Both?. Both!?.
我不能要两只猫
I can't have two cats!
乔伊才是那种会要两只猫的人
Joey's the kind of guys who could have two cats.
晚安，甘瑟
Goodnight, Gunther.
我没有领养猫
I didn't get a cat.
真有趣
That's interesting.
不，那一点都没有趣 那非常非常没有趣
No,it's not "interesting." It's very,very not interesting.
事实上那百分之百是没有趣，瑞秋
It's actually 100% the opposite of interesting.
好，我懂了，罗斯
I got it,Ross.
你没有权利告诉我说 你曾经喜欢过我
You had no right to say you had feelings for me.
在我发现之前 我跟茱莉过得很快乐
I was doing great with Julie before I knew!
在我发现之前 我也过得很快乐
I was doing great before I knew about you!
你以为看你跟茱莉那样 我心里好受吗？
You think it's easy to see you with Julie?
你应该在我认识她之前说出来
You should've said something before!
那时我不知道啊 那你为何从不说什么呢？
I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything?
因为总没有机会
There was never a good time.
对，你有一年机会 我们每晚都在一起混
You only had a year. And we only hung out every night!
不是…
Not...
…每个晚上
...every night.
而且我也不是没试过，瑞秋 但是每次都有事情发生
It's not like I didn't try. But things got in the way.
就像是意大利人啊…
You know,like ltalian guys...
…或者是前任的未婚夫啦…
...or ex-fiances...
…或者意大利人啊
...or ltalian guys.
只有一个意大利人 你到底有没有重点啊？
There was one ltalian guy,okay? And do you have a point?
重点是 我现在已经不需要这个了
The point is,I don't need this right now!
太迟了
Okay? It's too late.
我在跟别人交往，我很快乐 这艘船起航了
I'm with somebody else. I'm happy. This ship has sailed!
你喜欢什么时候撇开对我的感情都可以吗？
You're just gonna put away your feelings for me?
我从九年级就开始这样了 我早驾轻就熟了
I've done it since ninth grade. I'm good at it.
那好，你尽管去做吧，罗斯
All right,fine. You go ahead and do that.
我告诉你，我不需要你的蠢船
I don't need your ship!
好 好
-Good. -Good!
你知道吗？我现在了结了
And you know what? Now I got closure!
试试下面那个
Try the bottom one.
莫妮卡，现在是早上六点半
Monica,it's 6:30 in the morning.
我们不再去运动，结束了
We're not working out. It's over.
怎么啦？只剩一磅，来啦
No way! With one pound to go? Come on!
我们运动，我们移动 我们在其中舞动
We're workin',we're movin' We're in the zone,we're groovin'
我不在乎我的最后一磅
I don't mind the last pound.
我很喜欢这最后一磅
In fact,I kind of like the last pound.
所以不要逼我 做下终生遗撼的事
So don't make me do anything that I'll regret.
那你要做什么，肥仔？
What you gonna do,fat boy?
什么？
What?
没什么，除了告诉你 我觉得你精力这么充沛真棒
Nothing. Except tell you it's wonderful how much energy you have.
谢了
Well,thanks.
尤其是想到你现在去找工作多么得焦头烂额
Especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.
你不能告诉你父母你被开除了 因为他们会非常的失望
You can't tell your parents you were fired,because they'd be disappointed.
尤其你又没有男朋友 可以借肩膀让你哭
It's not as if you have a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.
没有，但是我…
Well,no. But l....
我是说，如果是我的话 我想我会连起床都会很困难
If it were me,I'd have difficulty getting out of bed at all.
我试着保持乐观
You know,I try to stay positive.
那么…
So you....
你想出去跑一跑吗？
You feel like going for a run?
好吧
All right.
你不一定要去跑的 你可以在这里睡一下
Because you don't have to. You could just take a nap right here.
-只睡一小会儿 -好
Just for a little while.-Okey